Guide to the Levy Dime Novel Collection 1821-1968 Levy
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Periodicals (Box 92-122)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XVI City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: 1901 (Box 97, Folder 2054)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XVIII City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1903 (Box 97, Folder 2055)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XIX City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1904 (Box 97, Folder 2056)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XX City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1905 (Box 98, Folder 2057)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XXI City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1906 (Box 98, Folder 2058)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XXV City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1910 (Box 98, Folder 2059)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XXVI City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1911 (Box 98, Folder 2060)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XXVII City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1912 (Box 98, Folder 2061)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XXIX City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1914 (Box 98, Folder 2062)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XXX City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1915 (Box 98, Folder 2063)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: vol. XXXI City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1916 (Box 98, Folder 2064)
  - Series Title: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Almanac Series Number: XLI City: Brooklyn Publisher: Brooklyn Daily Eagle Format: hard cover Date: January, 1926 (Box 98, Folder 2065)
  - Series Title: The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine Series Number: vol. LIII, no. 4 City: New York Publisher: The Century Co. Date: February, 1897 (Box 98, Folder 2066)
  - Series Title: The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine Series Number: vol. XXXVII, no. 1 City: New York Publisher: The Century Co. Date: November, 1888 (Box 98, Folder 2066)
  - Series Title: Chambers's Journal containing the novel of Walter's Word and numerous instructive and entertaining articles City: London and Edinburgh Publisher: W. & R. Chambers Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 98, Folder 2067)
  - Author: Steve, Shadow Title: The frozen face or Dick Dobbs among the smugglers Series Title: The Millionaire Detective Dick Dobbs Detective Weekly Series Number: 7 City: New York Publisher: George Marsh Company Date: May 1, 1909, undated (Box 99, Folder 2068)
  - Series Title: Donahoe's Magazine Series Number: vol. XLI, no. 1 City: Boston Publisher: Donahoe's Magazine Co. Date: January, 1899 (Box 99, Folder 2069)
  - Series Title: The Eclectic Magazine of Foreign Literature, Science, and Art Series Number: New Series, vol. IX City: New York Publisher: E. R. Pelton Format: hard cover Date: January-June, 1869 (Box 99, Folder 2070)
  - Series Title: The Eclectic Magazine of Foreign Literature, Science, and Art Series Number: New Series, vol. XXXIII City: New York Publisher: E. R. Pelton Format: hard cover Date: January-June, 1881 (Box 99, Folder 2071)
  - Series Title: The Eclectic Magazine of Foreign Literature, Science, and Art Series Number: New Series, vol. XXXIV City: New York Publisher: E. R. Pelton Format: hard cover Date: July-December, 1881 (Box 99, Folder 2072)
  - Series Title: The Eclectic Magazine of Foreign Literature, Science, and Art Series Number: New Series, vol. XXXVII City: New York Publisher: E. R. Pelton Format: hard cover Date: January-June, 1883 (Box 99, Folder 2073)
  - Series Title: The Eclectic Magazine of Foreign Literature, Science, and Art Series Number: New Series, vol. XXXVIII City: New York Publisher: E. R. Pelton Format: hard cover Date: July-December, 1883 (Box 99, Folder 2074)
  - Series Title: Emerson's Magazine and Putnum's Monthly Series Number: vol. VI City: New York Publisher: Oaksmith & Co. Format: hard cover Date: January-June, 1858 (Box 99, Folder 2075)
  - Series Title: Everybody's Magazine Series Number: vol. II, no. 1-12; vol. 3, no. 1-12 City: Albany, NY Publisher: D. R. Niver Format: hard cover Date: undated (Box 99, Folder 2076)
  - Series Title: Everybody's Magazine Series Number: vol. III, no. 12 City: New York Publisher: The North American Company Date: August 17th, 1899 (Box 99, Folder 2077)
  - Title: The Family Friend Series Title: New Series Series Number: vol. II City: London Publisher: Houlston and Stoneman Format: hard cover Date: 1852 (Box 100, Folder 2078)
  - Series Title: Frank Leslie's Pleasant Hours Series Number: vol. XXX, no. 5 City: New York Date: June, 1881 (Box 100, Folder 2079)
  - Series Title: Frank Leslie's Pleasant Hours. Devoted to Light and Entertaining Literature. Series Number: vol. XLI City: New York Publisher: Mrs. Frank Leslie, Publisher Format: hard cover Date: 1887 (Box 100, Folder 2080)
  - Series Title: Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly Series Number: vol. II, no. 1-6 Format: hard cover Date: July-December, 1876 (Box 100, Folder 2081)
  - Series Title: Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly Series Number: vol. IX City: New York Publisher: Frank Leslie's Publishing House Format: hard cover Date: January-June, 1880 (Box 100, Folder 2082)
  - Series Title: Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly Series Number: vol. XIII City: New York Publisher: Frank Leslie's Publishing House Format: hard cover Date: January-June, 1882 (Box 100, Folder 2083)
  - Series Title: Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly Series Number: vol. XXXIII City: New York Publisher: Frank Leslie's Publishing House Format: hard cover Date: January-June, 1892 (Box 100, Folder 2084)
  - Series Title: Frank Leslie's Sunday Magazine Series Number: vol. VI City: New York Publisher: Frank Leslie's Publishing House Format: hard cover Date: July-December, 1879 (Box 100, Folder 2085)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 1-16 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Format: hard cover Date: 1878 (Box 100, Folder 2086)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 2 c. 1, 2 c. 2, 3 c. 1, 3 c. 2 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: 1878 (Box 101, Folder 2087)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 17, 23, 30 c.1, 30 c. 2, 30 c. 3 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: 1878 (Box 101, Folder 2088)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 41, 45, 54, 59 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Format: hard cover Date: February 14, 1879; March 7, 1879; April 25, 1879; May 23, 1879 (Box 101, Folder 2089)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 66-69 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: July 11-August 1, 1879 (Box 101, Folder 2090)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 70-72, 74 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: August 8-22, September 5, 1879 (Box 101, Folder 2091)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 76 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: September 19, 1879 (Box 101, Folder 2092)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 57, 46, 100, 92 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: May 9, March 7, December 19, November 28, 1879 (Box 101, Folder 2093)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 97, 98, 32, 57, 107, 112, 131, 132, 140, 143, 144, 146 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Format: hard cover Date: misc., 1878-80, 1878-1880 (Box 101, Folder 2094)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 95, 103, 110 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: December 5, 1879; January 9, February 27, 1880, 1879-1880 (Box 101, Folder 2095)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 117, 121 c. 1, 121 c. 2, 122 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: April 16, May 14, 21, 1880 (Box 101, Folder 2096)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 130, 140, 57a c. 1, 57a c. 2 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: July 16, September 17, October 8, 1880 (Box 101, Folder 2097)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 150, 151 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: November 26, December 3, 1880 (Box 101, Folder 2098)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 159, 164, 166 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: January 28, March 4, 11, 1881 (Box 101, Folder 2099)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 195, 202 c. 1, 202 c. 2 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: July 8, August 26, 1881 (Box 101, Folder 2100)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 203, 208, 209 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: September 2, October 7, 14, 1881 (Box 101, Folder 2101)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 223, 227 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: January 6, 27, 1882 (Box 101, Folder 2102)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 229, 246, 284 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: February 3, April 21, December 1, 1882 (Box 101, Folder 2103)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 287, 305, 310 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: December 22, 1882; April 13, May 4, 1883, 1882-1883 (Box 101, Folder 2104)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 329, 351, 389 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: August 17, December 21, 1883; August 1, 1884, 1883-1884 (Box 102, Folder 2105)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 435, 451, 499 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: December 26, 1884; February 6, November 20, 1885, 1884-1885 (Box 102, Folder 2106)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 510, 518, 575 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: February 5, April 2, 1886; April 8, 1887, 1886-1887 (Box 102, Folder 2107)
  - Series Title: Franklin Square Library Series Number: 604, 609 City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: October 14, November 18, 1887 (Box 102, Folder 2108)
  - Series Title: The Galaxy Series Number: vol. II, no. 4 City: New York Publisher: Sheldon & Co. Date: April 1871 (Box 102, Folder 2109)
  - Series Title: Greenback's Periodical Library, containing in the cheapest possible form, a republication of new and standard works: voyages, travel, history, biography, select memoirs, popular science, personal adventures, tales of unexceptionable moral bearing, and approved forms Series Number: vol. I City: Philadelphia Publisher: T. K. Greenbank Format: hard cover Date: 1833 (Box 102, Folder 2110)
  - Series Title: The Half-Hour. A monthly publication for the home Series Number: vol. I, no. 10 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: July, 1898 (Box 102, Folder 2111)
  - Series Title: The Half-Hour. A monthly publication for the home Series Number: vol. 2, no. 2 City: New York Publisher: George Munro's Sons Date: November, 1898 (Box 102, Folder 2111)
  - Series Title: Harper's New Monthly Magazine Series Number: vol. XXXVII, no. CCXX City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Other Notes: fragment Date: September, 1868 (Box 102, Folder 2112)
  - Series Title: Harper's New Monthly Magazine Series Number: vol. X, no. LVI City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: January, 1855 (Box 102, Folder 2112)
  - Series Title: Harper's New Monthly Magazine Series Number: vol. LII, no. CCCVIII City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Date: January, 1876 (Box 102, Folder 2112)
  - Series Title: Harper's New Monthly Magazine Series Number: vol. LXX City: New York Publisher: Harper & Brothers Format: hard cover Date: December, 1884-May, 1885, 1884-1885 (Box 102, Folder 2113)
  - Series Title: Hours at Home: a popular monthly, devoted to religious and useful literature Series Number: vol. I City: New York Publisher: Charles Scribner & Co. Format: hard cover Date: May-October, 1865 (Box 102, Folder 2114)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XXII, no. 9 Other Notes: fragment Date: March, 1862 (Box 102, Folder 2115)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XIX, no. XII Date: December, 1859 (Box 102, Folder 2115)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XI, no. 4 Date: February, 1851 (Box 102, Folder 2115)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XXIII, no. 1 Date: January, 1863 (Box 102, Folder 2115)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XIX, no. XI Date: November, 1859 (Box 102, Folder 2115)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XI, no. 25 Date: September, 1851 (Box 102, Folder 2115)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XVI City: Boston Format: hard cover Date: 1856 (Box 102, Folder 2116)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Repository: a monthly periodical devoted to literature and religion Series Number: vol. XXV City: Boston Publisher: A. Tompkins Format: hard cover Date: 1857 (Box 102, Folder 2117)
  - Series Title: The Ladies' Wreath a magazine of literature & art Series Number: vol. VI, no. XII City: New York Publisher: J. M. Fletcher & Co. Date: April, 1852 (Box 102, Folder 2118)
  - Series Title: The Lady's Friend. A monthly magazine of literature and fashion Series Number: vol. VI, no. 6-8 City: Philadelphia Publisher: Deacon & Peterson Date: June-August, 1869 (Box 102, Folder 2119)
  - Series Title: The Lady's Friend. A monthly magazine of literature and fashion Series Number: vol. VI, no. 2-4 City: Philadelphia Publisher: Deacon & Peterson Date: February-April, 1869 (Box 103, Folder 2120)
  - Series Title: The Lady's Friend Series Number: vol. VI City: Philadelphia Publisher: Deacon & Peterson Format: hard cover Date: January-December, 1869 (Box 103, Folder 2121)
  - Series Title: The Lady's Magazine; or, entertaining companion for the fair sex, appropriated folely to their use and amusement Series Number: vol. XVII City: London Publisher: G. Robinson Date: January, 1786 (Box 103, Folder 2122)
  - Series Title: The Lady's Pearl; a monthly magazine, devoted to moral, entertaining and instructive literature, embellished with steel, copper and wood engravings, and music. Series Number: vol. III Publisher: P. D. & T. S. Edmands Format: hard cover Date: January-July, 1843; September-December, 1842, 1842-1843 (Box 103, Folder 2123)
  - Series Title: The Lady's Pearl; a monthly magazine, devoted to moral, entertaining and instructive literature, embellished with steel, copper and wood engravings, and music. Series Number: vol. III Publisher: P. D. & T. S. Edmands Format: hard cover Date: July, 1842-June, 1843, 1842-1843 (Box 103, Folder 2124)
  - Author: M., S. Title: Twice Lost Series Title: Library of Famous Fiction City: New York Publisher: R. Worthington Format: hard cover Other Notes: also contains For a woman's sake by Watts Phillips and Olive Varcoe by Mrs. Notley Date: 1881 (Box 103, Folder 2125)
  - Author: Notley, Mrs. Title: Olive Varcoe Series Title: Library of Famous Fiction City: New York Publisher: R. Worthington Format: hard cover Other Notes: also contains Twice Lost by S. M. and For a woman's sake by Watts Phillips Date: 1881 (Box 103, Folder 2125)
  - Author: Phillips, Watts Title: For a woman's sake Series Title: Library of Famous Fiction City: New York Publisher: R. Worthington Format: hard cover Other Notes: also contains Twice Lost by S. M. and Olive Varcoe by Mrs. Notley Date: 1881 (Box 103, Folder 2125)
  - Series Title: Lippincott's Monthly Magazine. A popular journal of general literature, science, and politics. Series Number: vol. XL City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Company Format: hard cover Date: July-December, 1887 (Box 103, Folder 2126)
  - Series Title: Lippincott's Monthly Magazine. City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Company Format: hard cover Other Notes: c. 1 Date: April, 1888 (Box 103, Folder 2127)
  - Series Title: Lippincott's Monthly Magazine. City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Company Format: hard cover Other Notes: c. 2 Date: April, 1888 (Box 103, Folder 2128)
  - Series Title: Lippincott's Monthly Magazine. City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Company Date: April, 1889 (Box 103, Folder 2129)
  - Series Title: Lippincott's Monthly Magazine. City: Philadelphia Publisher: J. B. Lippincott Company Other Notes: contains Captain Molly by Mary A. Denison Date: September, 1894 (Box 103, Folder 2130)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 463-6 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: April 2-23, 1853 (Box 103, Folder 2131)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1125 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: December 23, 1865 (Box 103, Folder 2132)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 823 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: March 10, 1860 (Box 103, Folder 2132)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1115 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: October 14, 1865 (Box 103, Folder 2132)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1116 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: October 21, 1865 (Box 103, Folder 2132)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 904 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: September 28, 1861 (Box 103, Folder 2132)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1444 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: February 10, 1872 (Box 103, Folder 2133)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1446 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: February 24, 1872 (Box 103, Folder 2133)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1363 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: July 16, 1870 (Box 103, Folder 2133)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1250 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: May 15, 1868 (Box 103, Folder 2133)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1251 City: Boston and New York Publisher: Littell, Son & Company Date: May 23, 1868 (Box 103, Folder 2133)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: vol. CLXXXIII City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Format: hard cover Date: October, November, December, 1889 (Box 103, Folder 2134)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1733-5, 1737, 1739 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: September 1-15, 29, October 13, 1877 (Box 105, Folder 2135)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1748 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: December 15, 1877 (Box 105, Folder 2136)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1750 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: December 29, 1877 (Box 105, Folder 2136)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1744 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: November 17, 1877 (Box 105, Folder 2136)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1742 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: November 3, 1877 (Box 105, Folder 2136)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1764, 1766-9 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: April 6, April 20-May 11, 1878 (Box 105, Folder 2137)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1772-3, 1775-7 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: June 1-8, June 22-July 6, 1878 (Box 105, Folder 2138)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1778, 1780-3 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: July 13, July 27-August 17, 1878 (Box 105, Folder 2139)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1784-6, 1788-9 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: August 24-September 7, September 21-8, 1878 (Box 105, Folder 2140)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1822, 1824-6, 1829 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: May 17,, May 31-June 14, July 5, 1879 (Box 105, Folder 2141)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1830-4 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: July 12-August 9, 1879 (Box 105, Folder 2142)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1836-40 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: August 23-September 20, 1879 (Box 105, Folder 2143)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1841, 1843-6 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: September 27, October 11-November 1, 1879 (Box 105, Folder 2144)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1848-50, 1852-3 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: November 15-29, December 13-20, 1879 (Box 105, Folder 2145)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 1854, 1955, 2288-90 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: December 27, 1879; December 10, 1881; May 5-19, 1888, 1879-1881 (Box 105, Folder 2146)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2291-5 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: May 26-June 23, 1888 (Box 105, Folder 2147)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2296, 2362, 2388-90 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: June 30, 1888; October 5, 1889; April 5-19, 1890, 1888-1889 (Box 105, Folder 2148)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2391-5 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: April 26-May 24, 1890 (Box 105, Folder 2149)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2396-2400 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: May 31-June 28, 1890 (Box 105, Folder 2150)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2798 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: February 19, 1898 (Box 105, Folder 2151)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2830 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: October 1, 1898 (Box 105, Folder 2151)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2520 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: October 15, 1892 (Box 105, Folder 2151)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2519 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: October 8, 1892 (Box 105, Folder 2151)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2900 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: February 3, 1900 (Box 105, Folder 2152)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2898 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: January 20, 1900 (Box 105, Folder 2152)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2896 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: January 6, 1900 (Box 105, Folder 2152)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2844 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: January 7, 1899 (Box 105, Folder 2152)
  - Series Title: Littell's Living Age Series Number: 2947 City: Boston Publisher: Littell and Co. Date: December 29, 1900 (Box 105, Folder 2153)